cartmanager.net 2014-12-15

# Online Shopping Carts, Shopping Cart Software - Privacy Policy

  |  |    
|  | 

**CartManager Online Shopping Cart Software Web Site Privacy Policy** CartManager ("CartManager", "we", "our", "us") values your privacy and endeavors to treat your personal information with due care and security. Our Privacy Policy sets forth the ways in which CartManager obtains and uses your personal information. CartManager reserves the right, without notice, to modify or eliminate all or a portion of this Privacy Policy at any time. By making use of the CartManager website or any CartManager product or service, you agree to the terms of the Privacy Policy in its ongoing form.

CartManager may collect information directly from you in order to provide products or services, to administer customer service assistance, or to fulfill any legal or regulatory requirements. CartManager may also obtain personal information as a result of a consumer's financial transactions using the CartManager product(s) or through a merchant that uses the CartManager products and/or services. With respect to any information a CartManager merchant may provide, CartManager will treat the information in accordance with the terms and conditions of the CartManager online Service Agreement, which may be viewed at: <http://www.cartmanager.net/administration/termsagreement.php3>

CartManager may store the information that you provide. This information may include, for example, your name, mailing address, e-mail address and telephone number, as well as certain interactive data such as the type of browser you use, the files you request, or the domain or IP address you use to access our website(s). If you supply us with personal data or request information from us, we may use your information to respond to your request. If you are a CartManager merchant you may receive third-party email notifications and/or offers relating to products or services in which CartManager believes you may have an interest. You can change the preference settings in your CartManager account at any time.

CartManager limits access to your personal information to those CartManager employees and business clients that need the information in order to provide our products and services to you. If you are a CartManager merchant, we may share your information with outside parties for such purposes as (by way of example and not of limitation) obtaining credit reports, performing customer verifications, and administering underwriting and risk management functions. We will disclose your information in response to a valid request issued by a court, government agency or regulatory authority.

When we have a direct customer relationship with you, we will strive to make information available to you about the general uses of the information we collect. Generally, we publish or link to this information on web pages at the point of sale, through privacy notices on our websites, and by other means specified by applicable state and federal laws.

When we obtain personal information as part of our direct relationship with you, we will not share this information with non-affiliated third parties, except in the following circumstances:

  * In accordance with the CartManager Privacy Policy
  * To facilitate and complete merchant-initiated or authorized transactions
  * To comply with federal, state, and local laws, including credit reporting laws and credit card association rules
  * To investigate fraud
  * In the case of CartManager merchants, to offer products and services that CartManager believes may be of interest to you.

CartManager employs industry-standard security measures to protect personal information collected against unauthorized access, disclosure, alteration or destruction. These measures may include, without limitation, encryption, restricted internal access, physical access security, and other technologies. CartManager continually reviews and enhances its security systems in an ongoing effort to provide safe and secure treatment of its data.

As part of its products and services, CartManager may create links to third-party websites. CartManager is not responsible for the content or privacy practices employed by third-party websites that are linked to our website, nor does CartManager control or warrant the utility, merchantability, or workmanship of the products or services offered at third-party websites. Before you supply your personal information to a third-party website, whether or not the third party is a merchant, client, or partner of CartManager, you should review and understand the applicable privacy policy for that website.

The examples contained in this Privacy Policy are illustrations only, and they are not intended to be all-inclusive. If your CartManager account is terminated for any reason or if you become an inactive customer, our Privacy Policy will continue to apply. If you are a merchant using the CartManager product(s) or service(s), this Privacy Policy applies to all accounts you may have with us, and it replaces all our previous disclosures to you about our information practices.

If you have any questions about the CartManager Privacy Policy, please contact us using one of the methods available on the "Contact Us" page of the CartManager website.

The CartManager Privacy Policy applies only to persons or companies making use of the CartManager website, CartManager's shopping cart software, product(s), and/or services(s) in the United States of America. To the extent allowed by law, the same terms and conditions hereof apply to non-U.S. parties. However, additional terms and conditions under international laws and cross-border credit card association regulations may apply.  
  
---
